Letters orbit my breath
I'm drifting in the midnight ocean
No floor beneath the starry noise
Here up in zero gravity motion
I'm like wires learning how to voice
Knee and cymbals spill like meteor rain
They skim my skin, they leave a trace
Lightning stitching through my veins
A soft apocalypse on my face
I don't read the future
I'll call them
I must say
cult of Psyche show where the chat moves fast and the timelines move suspiciously
Pay the toll, roll the dice
Huh?
I'm on stream yard in the starfield cloak
Chat popping off, I'm dead paying no smoke
Open panel, strange guest
Truth gets told and drama lists in the background
Subtle in the gold
If you came for drama, sorry, wrong, right?
We do boundary magic with a velvet knife
Rules on the wall, watch the chaos behave
Cause boredom is a ban
Redepend, okay?
Of sight, pay the toll, roll the dice
Next, what time is it?
3-33 again, obviously
Later
As I pay the toll roll the dice
Please exit through the gift shop
Do not feed the trolls
Feed the cats
I have something to say to you
They're not even here anymore. I mean just
Like what is it? What is wrong?
Understand. I mean
Hold on a second. Oh, I mean first of all, I mean I just have like everything that something like one person says that it's like
you know
Let's see. Yeah, anything that one person says
That is is like just untrue and then everyone just keeps repeating it and it's just like really annoying stuff like that
like
I don't know. Will I am on like the today show or something explaining like how music works?
I think I might have to because everyone just is like, oh
Apparently, I'm just like the only person. I'm the only bad person in the world that like, you know
But dare, you know
Use technology to aid their
art
I don't know but um
But like I said
Yeah, I don't really play instruments that well.
You've probably played the Mary Haddle a little while.
I don't know if you can hear me right now, let me see.
But, don't put a lot of work into that.
That's kind of dumb of you.
Okay, but let me listen, let me listen, hold on.
Not like you in particular,
just like the perky people there.
You know who's chat I was at today?
This woman, Zara, I left her chat.
She used to be on my show and she was so nice and friendly.
I said hi to her in her chat. You know what she said to me nothing because she can't see me
She has me blocked for you over you. I don't I've never been to her chatting before yeah
But here let's look at let's listen to like and now you can listen to he think a musician and you know
I'm debate about how good of a musician will I am Rizzer? What's up? Is that Rizzer Rizzer?
Is that the Rizzer like that hot Iranian guy that's walking around Miami hitting on women? I do like that Rizzer
Is that you that you?
I don't know. I don't know, but that was pretty cool. Do you guys hear me? Hold on
Yeah, let's watch this real quick though
I just want to make a point. I tried to make this point before and then Carl's like, oh, I'm lazy
Yeah, how you know like the least lazy person is it's me. He just sat up for the next like last five hours
Talking doing this stupid coding trying to get something to work except for me. So I still do care
But Jesus, I mean some people some people right here look
Now, happy Halloween. Will, we've got to start with that.
Do gays have bumps?
No, because people say that all the time.
I know.
Has anyone checked the gays?
Never seen anything gays have bumps.
Can we get a gays, please, or a little ghost for where I am?
We want to check if it's got some bumps.
We're going to find this out by the end of the interview.
I promise you.
Well, it's so lovely to see you today.
Because you guys do.
Well, I mean, the O.J.,
do you tell me you still love it as much as you did when you started?
I love it. Seriously, I do.
Yeah? Yeah.
to be around like aspirational singers
that are looking to make a career out of their passion,
bring in joy, to be around that energy is refreshing.
It's like a jolt of energy all the time.
And there's a big change in this series, isn't there?
Yeah, we got groups.
Now you can have like groups.
So next year we're gonna have it too.
So if you wanna be on The Voice next year,
watch The Voice this year, but if you've got a group.
you come on the show I will I know you get this question all the time but what
are you looking for this year like I know you've seen so much talent pass
through those doors but what are you really looking for this year awesome
sauce or some sauce yeah some awesome sauce just a bit of sauce yeah lovely
bit of sauce yeah I mean everybody could use some sauce
Especially if you want to be the boss, you have to have souls.
No, you're not going to give anything away,
but even when we were watching that V10,
you're like, we got some great people this year.
You know, I don't know where they hide in the UK,
but right when you think you have an awesome year,
the next year is even awesomer.
Yeah.
There's a lot of great people that have come out of the voice as well.
I mean Becky Hill, one of my favorites, she was on the show a few years ago.
Yo, Becky Hill.
Yeah, big up Becky Hill, justice for Becky Hill.
That's what I say, it's about time.
There it is.
Are you still always constantly looking for the same mindset or do you go in completely open?
Never, never, I don't, I mean, except for like, if an awesome, you know, opera singer comes,
I like term for that because I know, you know, everyone's going to say.
I don't know what to do with that type of music, you know?
What kind of coach you are, you know?
I don't fully enough for me.
So I'm like, yo, boom.
You know, I like to press my button for, like, opera,
oddities, obscures, you know what I'm saying?
A little bit different.
Differentnesses.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Luffiness.
So that's the best way to impress you.
Go in, be a bit different.
Will I am just going to bang that button?
Yeah, because, like, you know, the other coaches
are going to keep it, like, traditional.
Well you are, you are totally different. I think you've, you'd, I've never come across somebody that
thinks just so outside the box like you, you don't think the same as everybody else. Have you
always known that about yourself? No, I'm like, and now thinking outside the box is like everybody
does that. Yeah. So now I think in the box and I kick the freaking edges and turn the box into a
circle. Now you can't even recognize the box. No, you spray sauce all over it on top. That's it.
in the acts on The Voice.
Your fellow coaches, you've got Oli, but Anne-Marie,
you've got Sir Tom as well.
I know that you're very close with them all.
The rivals up there and you've bashed your button
and Oli Merz or Anne-Marie turn around Sir Tom turns around.
I mean, what's your best pitch?
Do you think where you go,
I'm going to fight until I die until I get this one?
I like to, I don't really have like a strategy,
like up my sleeve.
I like to like, you know, you know, be a little bit like...
Fresh off the cuff improv a bit like soon as soon as they could predict you
It's, you know, it's predictable.
Yeah.
You'd rather just go with a flow.
Now, you're single with Britney Spears.
Mind your business, drop this song with Britney.
I mean, I've always liked working with Britney.
She's awesome.
We recorded that song originally in 2010.
Oh, my goodness. That's not long ago.
The lyrical part, yeah.
2007. I want to go 2011.
Why did it take so long to be released then?
The same reason why it takes a long time to go from grapes to grape juice to wine. Yeah
It's gonna make it better
Sometimes you got to let things ferment shout the song that you did with Britney as well
That was the one song that they used to play us in the Big Brother house. It's the only song we were allowed to hear
This is the only song so this is always mine. Yeah, look at that terrible
I absolutely love this show
Will as much as we love you working with Britney just release your new single as well. Let's go. Mmm. Tell us there's loads more music still to come
Yeah, I got music coming out
you know, pulling out singles as time goes on.
I got a song with Jay Balvin called Let's Go,
in collaboration with F1.
You know, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Getting a pop out, there we go.
Yeah, so Let's Go is out right now.
Check it out on all the VSPs.
You know, I'm really proud of that.
And you've worked with some amazing people.
Is there anyone still on your hit list
that you're sort of scoping around going,
I want to do a collab with you?
Rihanna.
Yes.
I did something with her called Photographs in the Past.
Beyonce I did the remix to break my soul. Yeah, oh my god, but to rock with them, you know
Currently love be awesome to do that. They're my favorites
And one thing and I remember watching a show that you were on and you were looking into ai
Um, what are the music industry?
So first, I think, I think musicians need to have a central place to work right now, musicians are working across five different platforms, not just musicians creative creatives in general, working off like a messenger and then digital asset management platform, email zoom.
Artists are going to be competing with not only like humans, you know, making some pretty fresh music in the next couple years
Do you think there needs to be some regulations on it? They will
There needs to be regulations that stifle innovation, of course.
The regulations that protect us across the whole field.
Yeah, your identities as well.
Like, the voice is that the AI can come up with concerns.
We've heard it online where we think it's someone's new single, and it's an AI.
Yeah, but what about if somebody calls you and you think it's somebody but it's not?
Yeah, look at that.
It's not really zooming.
Well, look.
Not only is your voice good for some music, but it's no where I am in our eyes.
You know, I like to look at it like...
You know, one day AI is going to do yoga,
but it ain't going to stretch for me.
You've got to stretch. Some things you've got to do yourself.
Absolutely.
Well, it's honestly so lovely to see you,
but there's someone else here that really wants to see you.
Well, I am.
Well, we've got to cook.
Well, surprise, surprise, well, we've got to cook.
Because it's CUNY at 6!
Yes!
I knew he was about to cook.
We know Will that you've got a very busy day so you can't stick around for cookery.
But this is apples.
They're awesome sauce apples.
Some vegan royal icing for you.
So it's vegan chocolate?
Yep.
Oh, that's awesome.
I'm sorry, that looks disgusting.
Sorry.
Vegan apple?
I mean, the apple's already in there.
Oh, thank you so much.
I don't know what the same interview I saw, but they did ask him about it.
I mean, because in the interview I saw, he was talking about, he's like, well, how about,
like, have you heard of jazz music?
Oh, shit.
Have you heard of jazz musicians, like from like the 20s, that like, I, he, he samples
a huge thing.
So I don't know.
I'm not, I can't keep explaining things.
He also said that we're creatives.
came to say musician and so they there's people in the recording industry that probably don't even play
music you know the guy there's a guy that writes like most of the number one hits he's swedish
i don't know if he plays any instruments he's just some dorky guy but he wrote like Justin Timberlake
And so there's something in the writing too.
It's just like having a blanket hatred of anything.
Like people just don't understand the tar
and since they're writing her songs.
I mean, she could, I mean, they're that bad
that it's like, okay, yeah, she could write that.
But no, they're professional people write her songs.
Anyway, so since nobody was here,
when I played my intro and people were saying,
Well, let's look. This is funny.
Sigh in the temple, cloak in the glow Ring on the halo, chest like the sun, let's go
Welcome to the coat, keep it cute, keep it tight
Drolls get bored when the moths move right
Vodka click, lifetime baths get shine
Chaos and order in the same damn shine
Dumb scrupe, top blood thump, I know my life will once a readin' tonight
We weird, we blessed, we loud, we nice
Cold as ice, pay the toll, roll the dice
I'm on stream yard in the starfield cloak
Chat popping off, I'm deadpan, no smoke
Open panel, strange guests
Truth gets told and drama lists in the background
Subtle in the gold
If you came for drama, sorry, wrong, right?
We do boundary magic with a velvet knife
Rules on the wall, watch the quarterm is a ban
I'm a welcome to the cave
Redepend, okay?
On the mic, like who wants a ring tonight
We weird, we blessed, we loud, we nice
Cold of sight, pay the toll, roll the dice
Next, what time is it?
333 again, obviously
Late up, you online, I was born online, posted
Good morgue, got versions, baby, nothing stays dead
If the robots take exacted up, we bonk it on the head
Omari, dragana, pati, termeric
Glow, forearms, one vibe
If you hate joy, then you cannot get in Gifted memberships rain, like confetti in June
I got a hundred plus and still want the moon Kickstarter dreams in a chaos coated
We turn head-close into silence and we wave bye-bye
Welcome to the co-keep it cute, keep it tight
Trolls get bored when the mods move, right?
Vote or click, lifetime badge that shines
Chaos and order in the same damn shrine
No I'm scurred, tabla thumps, circus lights
Psyche on the mic, life who wants arena
As I pay the toll, roll the dice
What?
Please exit through the gift shop
Rolls
Feed the cats
No
Can I say so riz hold on you are the guy or you're not the guy
Electra the one that got away. I don't know our electorate is I absolutely have you have the epilepsy probably not the best thing to watch
Look at the screen directly, but
Yeah, I'd like that one though. Hey Rick. No, I think was so riz. I think this is guy. He's walking around, Florida
He's real hairy
Um, but I and then I kind of a cute way. Hey, what's up a lecture? How are you sweetheart? Yay
So, um, so I was sharing his show yesterday. I was sharing Danny in this move. It was a quite a day
I got extremely drunk and today I had an invitation to his discord like he just found me. I don't know if he was on mine already
but hey
It's serendipity. I was like, hey, I
But I was like, where's Alisa Jordana? I didn't yeah, I'm sorry. I didn't see like, you know, I'm a
I'm really doing a lot lately.
I've been working so hard on this website
and it's just like one, even with coding,
like a thousand times easier, it's still not easy.
It's still like a lot of work.
Thank you, thank you, yeah.
And that was just for like people that are like,
oh, not another, it's like,
it's supposed to be like something to introduce the show.
And I know I played a lot of stuff,
I'm trying to get feedback that's really for my but I had to kind of just start but you know what I
Know I know I have some I know I know there's something there. Well website pull it up
Are you talking about Riz is on he's on kick. It's the the riser or something. Well, I can look it up
Hold on you know, I'll show you some of this show because it was really good
Hold on a second. I remember it's called the riser. You'd like to thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Yeah, and that's good because now it's like we I have built up like a good amount of inside jokes
in the show and so it's kind of like
material rights itself in a little way
Um, what was it was like Riz cam or something? Oh my gosh the channel's funny though because he goes up to these like
Hey, I have beautiful lady. Hey, I mean beautiful lady and remember when I went to the pier and was trying to get people to talk to me
Kind of is like that
Is it a Riz cam?
Let me see.
Yeah, it is.
It's Riz Cam.
You can see him.
He's hairy, he's beautiful, but he has a show
and here he is talking to girls.
He says he looks like Chewbacca and picking up girls.
You're gonna see?
He's really funny.
Oh, that's Danny.
Yeah, you're like Dano.
Hold on, here we go.
But look at this, you can already tell
it's gonna be a good show.
Look, look at that, look at that beautiful back.
How's it be, ma'am?
You've got such beautiful hair.
Her hair?
Look at that butt.
My God, no, thank you.
OK, you're taking it?
I'll take it?
Yeah.
All right, have a good day.
Excuse me, ma'am. You are absolutely stunning. What's your name? Liz. Liz, what are you up to today?
Just chilling, friends. Chilling? Where are you from? The beach. Um, here in Liverpool.
Do you speak another language? I got there initially. Oh, eres muy hermosa.
Gracias. Um, what do you do for fun?
That's what I said. We found Bigfoot.
We took a bar, you know, enjoy the day out, sun.
so you said what are we doing we run the wrist cam so we're trying to show guys to be more confident
so i'm showing guys like hey it doesn't matter if you got this persian sweater you can go up
to a beautiful girl and say what's up hey it's always nice to say hi can i be your persian prince
this weekend no i'm married all you're married you're a very lucky man he sure is you have a great
What's happening guys? Are you everything okay?
That's Rizzer that comes in the cat. Oh look at those pups. Look at those Alex!
Where are you guys up to today?
Yeah, where are you guys from?
Palm Springs. What brings you out here?
Just hanging out. Yeah. Vacation. Vacation. What's the vacation? Just cuz? Yeah, just girl shirt. Yeah, you guys are all very beautiful.
Are you guys single? I'm not. You are? What's your name? Issa. Is that Latina?
Yeah. Oh, eres muy hermosa. Thank you.
Yo quiero que tú estás mi novia. No, thank you.
Thank you, my girlfriend.
Oh, you guys are great there.
I'm warming up, guys. I'm warming up.
And he has a good confidence about it, right?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Another Riz guy. I know a lot of guys.
I know, I do it.
Excuse me, man. You look fantastic. You are so beautiful. What's your name?
Marcella.
Marcella. Where are you from?
Seattle.
Seattle? Well, part of Seattle, like West Seattle.
That's like the little island area with the bridge, right?
Where's my car?
So you're more of a chiller.
Yes, West Coast.
What are you out here?
Sunshine.
Sunshine?
I'm not got my coat.
Is it raining right now in Seattle?
Yes, yeah.
But I've lived here for nine years now.
Oh, you've lived here for nine years?
Okay.
Brad, look.
What are you up to today?
just got to walk in Mission Beach to PB. Okay. Do you walk often? Yeah. We should go for a walk
sometime. I'm currently taking and expecting so. Oh my god. Congratulations. They're already
expecting us. They're like married. Amazing. We love to hear that guys. Shout out to her.
Ladies, you guys can't leave yet, I just got here.
No, they always leave me.
What's your name?
Oh, what are we interviewing for, please?
Well, we're running the risk cam.
So does beautiful woman like yourself.
What are you up to today?
We're tanning.
Tanning?
You look pretty tan.
Thank you.
That's the goal.
Are you from this area?
No, I live in Texas.
Texas.
How long are you here for?
14 days.
That's a pretty good vacation.
Did you are you gonna go surfing mm-hmm probably where are you gonna hit?
Probably germiline, maybe black
Maybe sunset blocks is a really good one. Are you gonna go naked Harry?
Probably not like ball. It's a nude beach. Not with the wax board
That sounds terrible. Where you go should we yeah
It is galley. I want to take you for a Persian magic carpet ride. Oh god. You like my Persian carpet
I won't pass away.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
So, okay.
How about if you're watching?
If you can watch this myself,
if you can find me,
if you can find me.
Do you want to shave your body and then we can make a toupee for a thing that is and he'll just probably just wear it one time
Just for a laugh. Yeah, I would think I verbita like he's in California
She's in California the most Persian, you know, they might bond over some of the political stuff right now
Like I still call it Persia some people called it Iran I think assistant Joe. Yeah, he's a Persian carpet
Yeah, I can show you the world
Thing that is and there's be
That's the only Middle Eastern people that I know as he calls this Harry Chess his Persian carpet
I know I call yeah, it's more like a person
What are those rugs that are like, you know real real like long or those remember those rugs from the 70s
They're like real. What was it called? Iran is I know I think that was Ayatollah Khomeini like in disguise
Don't you think so? I think I might be
But I don't know yeah, I do I know I do like Persian people
Be the didn't ruin them for me. Like I said, I had like what are my best friends in the I went to a school for like seven years
It was like
Six to 12th grade, but I had a friend and she was she was Persian and they called themselves Persian. They didn't say Iran
They said we're Persian
And when you speak Farsi, we don't.
So I've heard all of this stuff before,
because there was a lot of them at my school.
But they were really nice.
They were really nice.
But there's only one girl at my school
that I was actually in kindergarten with her.
And then we were really in the same grade and stuff.
And she was from Egypt.
And she wore a burqa.
But that was the most Middle Eastern kind of vibe.
We got, you know, if Bita would have gone to my school,
it would have been,
because she's really into that music.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
Oh, talking about my music's bad.
Oh my God.
I want to hear Alexandra Mayer's singing
with Tommy James and Bita.
You know, I want to see that.
And then they can talk to me about my music, okay?
La, la, la, la, la, la.
Oh my god, it's like that's the sound you hear before a bomb typical. I mean, it's like I heard that that loud that noise
I would run I would like run away. I mean, it's
It's just like, you know ever since 9-eleven guys, I'm a little bit sensitive. No, I know. I know they have nothing
I don't mean things
I'm just saying
I don't know. I can't go making accusations, but George Bush just so guilty to me
But anyway, hey guys, what is this painting?
I need to get a painting like this of Alex in my house. Hold on.
Because Jeffrey Epstein of Bill Clinton, I mean, it's like, hey, you've never seen him before.
I mean, I'm sure you guys have all heard about this.
Where is this beautiful painting? Hold on.
It's in his house. I mean, guys, look at this.
And it's not like a great painting per se.
Like it's not like, like the art quality is just like really,
it looks like, you know, you got it at the mall
for like a few bucks, right?
It looks like it's just like a joke,
but I don't know.
Here look, what do you guys think?
Oh, did I get it right?
Hold on.
Probably didn't get it right.
Let me see.
I guess I need to try it one more time.
Oh guys, did you see this by the way? Read this while I'm looking for it. There you go.
And there are the serial killer zodiac signs. You can notice there's no capricorn or aquarius,
which are my main signs. There's none of those on there, but there's a lot of
Pisces and Gemini's on there for sure. Not to say anything, but I mean, I was kind of surprised.
I was kind of surprised a little bit.
Okay, but here here we go. Oh, it's beautiful. It isn't actually a beautiful piece of art
Let me see. Can I save the image save image? Okay. Hold on guys. I'm halfway there. I got it. I got it
Okay dot gpg
Guys, have you are you familiar that Jeffrey? I've seen was a collector of fine art
Now tell me was this generated by AI this let's just see
picture
Image, okay, but was this generated by AI? I need your honest opinion
Where the frick is it?
Downloads
In my desktop, okay, how can I not see it on my desktop like it's like very
Obvious
Wasn't this, wasn't that, okay.
See, I guess there's something that doesn't want me
to share this photo, but now I have to.
Now it's turning into a compulsion.
Uh-oh, what do I do?
Now I have to show you, because you're gonna be like,
oh, you're just chickened out of showing it.
No, I'm not gonna chicken out, I'm gonna show it.
I'm gonna fucking show it, hold on a second.
Okay, now I see what happened.
It didn't save, right?
So I need to find another copy of it.
And I find another copy of this picture.
Yes, I can
Okay, I got it. I got it
Save image. Please. Please. Please. Yes. Yes. Yes. This will work and desktop. Oh, it's already there. I saved it
I saved it. Hold on
It was on my download. It's my downloads. Okay. Here we go. Look
Downloads and I like Bill Clinton, but look at this guys
I mean, this doesn't look like they're kind of stupid though.
It's like, it's obviously not.
It's like, just like, and it's like such a bad photoshop.
It's like, how about like a nice wig and makeup?
Like, and is that the Monica Lewinsky dress?
How does he have that?
You know?
It's like, you know why I say like, I feel like, you know,
I'm being played for a fool sometime by the media.
It's like, they're supposed to, we're supposed to believe.
That that was like they say it's a painting. Hey, it's a person. It's not a painting. It's a very it's very cheap
cheaply made photograph. Okay
Bill Clinton looks awful awful awful awful
I mean, how about a little lipstick, a little, a wig,
a Hillary wig, I mean, a Monica Lewinsky wig on it.
That'd be funny.
Like, it's just like, that was probably just used
for blackmail, and he'd be like,
I'm gonna show this to everybody unless, you know,
you come on my plane and get a massage from a 14 year old.
And that's why Bill Clinton's in the trouble he is today.
But you know what?
We knew he was like this when that whole Monica Lewinsky thing happened. Don't we didn't we we all saw this coming
We knew he'd be he would be on those flight logs. We did and we knew Hillary would be too
And Bill Bill Gates to and Bill like didn't like not I say Bill Gates like gave his wife an STD
and then Jeffrey Epstein contacted his wife and said oh, I have the I have the
antidote for this for this STD your husband
gave you from some like, you know, third world sexy had.
I mean, I don't understand and they're like,
oh, it's embarrassed.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, we had Prince Andrews on the floor.
It looks like he has the, the resuscitation Annie doll,
but it's actually like a young Russian.
I mean, she's in her twenties, thank God.
But yeah, I mean, she does,
Annie has a little bit more cleavage than...
And that woman, it just kind of disturbed me.
It just didn't look right.
It just didn't look right, right?
Yeah, he honestly said, he's like,
oh, I want to give you this antidote.
It's like, isn't it like a spy movie or something?
And then there's all these spies involved too.
Now I find out Bida had some Israeli friend in front of school.
Oh, this explains so much.
What, next?
Oh, yeah, oh, you have dual citizenship too.
I mean, please.
Oh, well, I don't I've said enough. I've said I've said enough. No, I love I love I love I love Jewish people. I love Jewish people
But I love I love people in general. There's not like a person. It's not because they're Jewish except for like I do like the sense of humor
But everyone there's lots of people it's good sense the humors
Hey
Gilgames Island isn't written by Sherwood Schwartz for for nothing, right?
He made the whole damn show
Yeah, World War three has begun you think ah
Hmm. I think we've been kind of been in it for it's like World War three is gonna be that undefined of a war
There's just it's just like a lot of like different things. It's like it's like it's like it's like been going on for a while
It's like when they said when they started saying war on terror as they will cable that name for something that means nothing
Boo, that's like I just hair. I that's terror right there
That's you're not sure about that. It was a World War three or that is like, you know, no terrorism is like, oh, I'm scared
It's like
That's what the war was on. We're doing a war on like what?
How did that go? What was that about? All I did all I thought I saw was a bunch of naked black guys getting strip searched
In the airport because of that because of that. It's different. I'm not a different person. I'm not a different
I'm just feeling
I guess got someone set me off tonight, but yeah, there's okay. I don't want to get in trouble
but
Yeah
Did they I mean it's like yeah, but yeah, okay you I think probably military people die every single day
So you can say every single day you can say, you know, United States service person has died today, right three or five
Yeah, I mean, that's called that's called like the military, you know
like
That's what they wanted to do, right?
It's like, and that's part of like the
three and five critically wounded.
Well, I mean, just think about like
how many billions of people there are in the world, right?
And maybe hopefully there are DNA will live on
or something, because they have very brave DNA.
Alexander's gonna protect me.
Can you two?
And Arthur?
I think I need you all to move in we can't we're gonna do like the threes company except
Jack is gay and so is everybody else that comes to live with them
But we would go to the eagle beagle. So alright, so I say I really don't know much about politics
And so I'm gonna be very very careful. I don't I just don't know I
Know beat is all excited about it and stuff like that. Yeah, I mean, it's okay. Yeah, cuz they don't like
Like that Sharia, you know, there's this thing called Sharia, which is like it's religious law and it's very
Hard it's hard on women, but it's also very hard on homosexuals too. Like in Iran you can they have gay marriage
It's legal, but they don't care which one but one of you gonna be getting a sex
Like you have to I mean, it's like that's the thing then you can be then it's like not gay
Because they had you know that but otherwise no, I'm serious
There's a HP whole HBO thing about it and the guy was like well
I don't really they both kind of like weren't like we're not interested in becoming a drag queen
But then the guy was like okay
Well, let's go I'll get this he didn't mind getting in the Birka and stuff
He's like oh, it's like you know kind of like just like a warm sweater, but he's like I I think in private
We'll just be ourselves. I I don't know. It's it's very difficult. It's very difficult
Yeah, but it's like also
Is it too different than the Puritans of America like people are saying?
Oh the pilgrims left because they're being religiously persecuted. Yeah, because they were so weird
There are like these there like these cult members like worse than this my cult and they're like get out of get out of England
You're scaring everybody
We're all black and praying all the time
And so that's what happened and then they came over here and then look at the sort of witch hunts
Right. I have an ancestor. Her name is her name is Mary Samford and she was actually unalive
She was hung because she danced around a tree drinking a
Thing of wine or beer or something like that. I'm singing to the devil
Or they said she probably was just a Quaker
So you were your very best Van Houston shirt and you're now messenger core your job back in the day
Who's that? Who's real real bond a Ralph Ralph bond?
Is, are you Rizzer?
Are you Rizzer?
Yeah, there are wackos, weirdos with beardos.
And you know what?
How about the hippies?
How weird were they, just like these spoiled white people,
you know, that were like,
oh, the man is keeping me damp, like the man.
Like, you know, it's like they had like,
they just like, everyone was like,
they're like the fucking like Republican grandfather
or something.
The man is, it's a man doing everything.
And I don't know if it was all, what's wild?
Yeah, the Chinese buffet what well the Chinese will not be eating me nor any of my cats
but
I'm hungry for Chinese food
table for four
God he then will have will have a cop a mobster a gay and
Whoever else comes whatever they are probably to do
What's up, God? Good to see you. Great to see you. How's everyone doing tonight? Yeah, I had a pretty good day
I was trying to
What what Canada dry? What don't you get? I don't like how you get confused
They got nobody else is doing question marks like what you have to rewind a little bit
We have inside jokes here. That's why it's called a cult and you're not around enough anymore
You want to go money for 20s panel and you want to fight with Christine and stuff?
Christine is a integral part of my show. You better be nicer from no one your butt is out of here. I
Didn't invite you to the table
Look, you're Canadian. It will take you the hours to drive over. It's like, you know
Listen, we're not gonna wait for you to get on your your mountie your horse
And come meet us and stuff like I know and it's like you just probably live out
You're probably in the middle of nowhere you up and no one wants to wait for you. You have it. He has a channel
When did this happen?
What is it doing his channel? He like used livestock Commission's helicopter
They have what they have a livestock Commission that has let's you use that yeah, of course
Look at everyone's a mod everyone's a mod in here
I have everyone has to be a mod or else they'll be kicked out of the show
I have just everyone's like a rogue mod. I have like
My mods are like the most vicious mods, but only for themselves
They don't care if anyone says anything to me, but if anyone says anything to them
They're done. This person is done. That person is done unless they're a mod too. So I had to make everyone a
Think I yeah even live with even live with them. That's cool
I do want to support like Canada dry my friend Danny yesterday like or yeah, I was on Friday
Was it right? It was Saturday actually. Yeah
You have your see if you're psych. I still have my Canada dry sketches
Yeah, you never remember I said can you send me that the picture of it? And what didn't I look kind of on it?
I don't remember exactly. I just remember
I don't know how much they look like me, but I don't know how much mine look like you the best picture
I did was a Fawzi
Christine's dog you remember everything Riz
Good it'd be somebody needs to hey guys by the way
It's so cool. Here's one of the coolest things I'm doing
Once I get it all working it's taking a while right but um, so I have this website called cult codex dot me
And that's gonna be my wiki. That's gonna it's gonna be
Here's what it does. It's gonna
Well, first of all, I'm gonna catalog for like 1600 shows, but here's what's gonna do. It's gonna it will like take it
It'll put it on a week a wiki page
This is not gonna be what Alexandra said words
Like I'm gonna be like working with Zaya and pebs to like blackmail everyone in the community
So they only will stream for us or something. That's that that is just a ridiculous theory
I mean, it's like she has good theory that one is one of that one's just kind of silly
But I mean, yeah, I mean, I don't know. I don't know. Okay, but anyway
Let's not let's not get me more trouble
Yeah, so, it's gonna have a summer,
so, but here's what it will have.
Everybody that comes on the panel,
like if your name is said, like,
oh, here's black, like on the panel,
you're gonna be quoted,
and what you say is gonna be up there.
Yeah, and so you guys will be getting these,
like, they're actually,
I found these really cute black letters,
and I put like this little mark,
because that's so, because it's black, and I'm just kidding.
Okay, yeah, and I'm putting these in,
and so if you wanna buy my silence,
I can take you off the wiki. It's gonna be about a hundred dollars person and a certain people will cost a lot more
Just for the regular viewer hundred dollars
No, you don't have to be on there
but yeah
Yeah, I
Mean I have to I mean it's like eventually we're all gonna be we're all gonna be blackmail
It's gonna it's like nobody's gonna be really able to do anything because it's like everyone will know everything might everybody
Know about you thing that is thing that is has a livestock fetish. I mean, what is that really like the fuck goats?
Like why like why do you have a catalog with a?
Mechanical goats like no her into your mail you receive. I
Was a little bit shocked you have a livestock fetish
Yeah
Yeah, this is oh this whole show remember when I remember I told the truth months ago when I said it the whole this whole show
Is just a big a big government like blackmail ring
Yeah, I'll drop the link. Okay
It's like I didn't I mean I had to figure it out. I wasn't I didn't like sign up for it, you know, I
Just a little while. Yeah, they're not it will and
Tell that to an Eskimo in Antarctica that loves barbecue penguin
They'll they'll say they're they'll say maybe they won't say it's left. It's a delicacy. Maybe how about that Japanese cow the Waigu?
The they actually massage this cow so it's meat is more tender imagine you get a massage and then you chop off your head
It's a pleasant day. Oh look it. We have a guest. Hold on
Japanese cow the
How holy fingers are like little little nobs. I'm typing so much
I
Get a lot of buildup of material and oh
You guys to drop the link this guy. I have no fingers anymore. I got no I got no little noobies
Yeah, well, I don't know. I mean, I just put a couple songs today. Like it's really hard like, you know, I'm trying to like
You know, can I try?
It's time to like you were leaving something, okay
What you're like, oh that I don't mind. That's weird. Don't leave the phone in the living room and go pee
Don't bring me why you're fucking peeing. I'm in my headset buddy. Oh
I heard something against the I heard like a like a sound against the your bull
Oh my god, oh holy shit your cock's that long. Yeah, I have to smack
I have to kind of hold it up so it doesn't touch the lip of the toilet, man.
That's holy shit, isn't the best part?
It's almost like you're getting a blow job from the toilet.
Wait, so you're hung like a horse basically. Yeah, I could actually
He barely wiped it wiped perfectly. I mean, are you circumcised or uncircumcised I'm uncut buddy. Oh my god uncut, which means
You have an aunt either
Yeah, it drips. Yeah, man. Nobody took anything from my penis. All right. So is that good or bad?
Jewish circumcised shit. It wasn't bad then people would not be getting circumcised. Hold on.
And I'll say this. No, I've heard I've heard a lot of women be anti-uncut until they deal with my cock
and they've always been like, you know, I've always thought uncircumcised cocks were not a thing. This is a great cock
I'm sorry I ever thought that they're amazing car. Yeah, there's no difference. The point is
I wish I could went to Harvard University or something
Did rabbis actually suck like blood out of cars? Yes, they do. It's called the moille. So there's a
moille and the moille. Oh my god. You're telling me this Harry lunatic is right
pull lectures, like, well, I'll take a little kid's
big bleeding. It's not the bleeding to stop the bleeding.
Oh, my God, he was right. Can we try this motherfucker was right
this whole time. Holy shit. Yo, thank you. This guy comes on
panel every day. Oh, this year when they're bleeding, we make
fun of what we think he's insane. And he's right.
It's like there's some kind of cleanliness thing to I mean even yeah, I'm not saying it's actual but
is still Nike. Do you want to
hear a real story about how it's
actually unhygienic? Some poor
why don't they do it? They'll stop
the bleeding. So they need to talk.
Then they suck it to stop the
child died of a herpes infection
because the rabbi suck the blood
out of it. Oh my god.
Yo, I didn't mean to take it this
fall. People are going to blood
transfusions. You can't be really
careful. Oh my god. I don't want
no rabbi sucking my dick.
Well, I like your legs on cut dick according to our uncut it's fine, baby
Boom gang says Jesus this conversation one left real quick. I had a clip of a lecture saying oh
And I had an orgasm and I like
I told that story, but I'm never telling a story on your show again
But thank you. You start from Simon. No psyche is a homegrown American
So let me tell you something when you're uncircumcised and erect
You're the shit come like it you looks like you're circumcised like that
Yeah, you guys are bugging
Yeah, it just dudes right out of the foreskin, right? And it's just a regular
Circumcised men sometimes do last longer because the tip of their
Have a more sensitive tip
because it's packaged. That's why they are you kidding helps them be less
sensitive water fucking and they last longer because they're the way
around. It has more feeling in it. Alice has all these nerve endings and
stuff on it. Your heart is cut. So it's good. You're losing your losing
sensation. But I'm coming right now at the same time. I think psyche already
came twice. I'm about to kind of
Are you doing over there bro?
I'm fucking right up. We didn't get here, baby. Chibi-chibi
I think I said a rain got bombed and here we are right like the rabbit hole just took us here
Like Rabbi some bloody cock
Sand people get involved everything goes to hell. You know that it's like it's just like oh my gosh
It's like dirt is when I blow everybody up all the plans are exploding. I mean, it's just it's nightmare, right?
We're at war my friends like this is big. This isn't something tiny
Back they weren't planning on that they plan to take out all the heads and they were gonna just be like, okay
We can surrender and I was like fuck you we do not and they're fighting back
And now I don't know what's gonna happen.
I mean, and it's like, of course they're tough.
I mean, it's like, I mean, there's not people.
At least they got, they're not pussy like fucking Venezuela.
At least they're fighting back.
Yeah, but it's like, this was scary.
Oh, I just came up, look at him.
Oh, flipping and ship it.
Yo, sweepy clip it.
I want to see sure hand.
You saw his hand make fun of his hand somehow.
And uh.
He's walking away into the darkness. So did you watch somebody you can definitely make fun of that somehow
So what we're gonna do up here. I don't know. I think I think World War two is probably like it's supposed to be as bad as it gets
Right, it's like that's I mean that was
Gas chambers and humans
It looks like it's no man, but still Ronis do is people dying in gas chambers equals one life like I like like
But it's controversial to say that stuff like that. I think the numbers are very exaggerated. I think a lot of it's I up
I think and Frank was really yeah, but I don't know so it's actually going on
You're right. Do we just know what they tell us on the bullshit news that they want us to see?
And Frank's diary had a checkerboard pattern on it. Oh, okay
it was a checkerboard pattern
representing what? the world?
chess
representing
obviously chess
black and white
good and evil
Hey, there's was oh, I'm in troubleshoot. Oh, my baby
My father did a DNA test and he had some Ashkenazi, okay, but so you're not his or what are you trying to tell him?
Yes, but if they have like, you know, you get 50% of your mom's DNA 50% of your dad's DNA
And so if you that had it, you'll have it too
It's like a small percentage
then it's like, I can just, there's some more,
something more blood.
You still have at least one percent of it.
Did your dad work in the mail industry?
In the mail?
No, he was a banker though.
a banker yeah and so that's very Jewish but he's actually his first wife
that's very Jewish
it really is though that was fun
his first wife was Jewish
her first wife she's a really nice lady she sounds like
yeah like that she's really cool but um you know um yeah like that was his first wife and so
that we didn't find out
there's to have Jewish and stuff and part Russian and stuff but it's really cool though
it's like um because I don't even think her mom knew that she was that
heavily like
Her mom was like a hundred percent Jewish, but uh, I
But actually you're Jewish. You have a little Jewish in you
You and it's probably like probably gonna say, oh, well, you know, you have to be like
But cesarean or like, you know, there's this there's certain kinds of like Ashkenazi and then like the other kind
But has anyone called beta and said hey beta. I'm sorry that your country's at war right now the poor girl
Is that okay? Right? She's from there, right? She has family there. Maybe they're killed yet. She's from Michigan
But they yes, you went there. What a dick. She's from Michigan. What a dick
Back there and then she went back. Oh
Yeah, we are and you can buy not exactly. Oh, you're right. You're right because I'm from fucking New York
So that's like saying if Columbia was on the war and my
Like have anyone called Alice like you from New York. Yeah, right. You're funny with that
Zi oh and ISM and the I but that the International Defense League or something like that
That's kind of sounds like like the much with the
What's that?
There's a council that met and it's like they're really scared. Oh, well, you can be
The trial lateral commission, you know the protocols of Zion's even more secret and scary
Meeting that was held like late 1800s and then that's a fake paper
it's
the
And so silly, you know, the Nazis went crazy, bro
You're not you okay, so you know, you know who the biggest, um, you know, so they had this this part of the army
Called the the SS or something like that like the special services or whatever
Do you know that that was up for conscription?
And so there's people from all over the world that went out there to fight for the for the germans and stuff like that
I mean, it's like so there's people
Black people. That's crazy to me. That happens now in Ukraine. There's Colombians there. There's Chinese people there people go there fight
Like from all over the world, but that's the world we live in right people have no minds and this guy would they fuck they want to do
Basically, that's what I
Came to terms with is that the Green Lantern? Hold on. Yeah, is that the Green Lantern Canada? No boys didn't hit it
We are clones of our parents. That's it. Look at yourself. You have to break those chains of your parents. I see it too
I'm like, yo, I'm exactly like my dad. Fuck. I'm exactly like that mother game. I'm not him
Like I know I'm not him. I feel I'm not my dad
But in so many ways I am and I'm just like my mom too like
Yeah, it sends the green, right?
Green in the black like a signal flare
Letters orbit my breath
I'm drifting in the midnight ocean
No floor beneath the starry noise
Hair up in zero gravity motion
Like wires learning how to voice
Knee and cymbals spill like meteor rain
They skim my skin, they leech
Stitching through my veins
A soft apocalypse on my-
Cause I don't read the future
It reads me back every cliff
A little doorway in the dark
And when my eyes go and roll
The silence starts to talk
Used to be a quiet planet
Keeping storms behind
Love this song. This is one of the best
Money for 20 money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money
I can't, because you have a green thing.
I like that, look at your little green, I love it.
Look, I'm reading to you, I have a green tree.
That's the green glass man.
Hey, I'm gonna also go, oh, okay.
I have a red, white, and blue speedo.
How about that?
Watch out for the green glass man.
Is he cute?
I might make a new fucking stream panel
called The Great Glass Man, and it just, it's just music.
I'm gonna make them cold
I was gonna make a
panel called
The great bald man, and it was hell of a story, but like a fairy tale ball
In reference to things that is
Because you have nice hair dick. Why would you do that? Why would you pull?
According to sweet peas ladies, I have no hair full of scabs and I'm
Yeah, she puts AI in my potential. I was like, I'm gonna take this bitch's channel down unless you take my strike off
And you know, you know what I said?
What did she do? Oh my God. Oh, she's funny. Funny when she does anything.
They don't do that. Notice how Peter doesn't do that. They use her to do that against you. They're so smart, too.
They don't want to do themselves, so they don't get fucked up.
Yeah, I think Bita
They used to say Bita sponsored like my Wikipedia page. No, she doesn't
YouTube page
$1 to my wiki
And by the way when you're walking on McDonald's, you know, we're gonna mention her again
And that would then I then I forgot I mean because she was
I was in the chat today a little bit and she wanted me to come up and like she but she was talking about me and stuff
So I mean, I have a right to
Talk to
Let it go but this woman is like she's like, oh, why leave me alone leave me alone
I don't have a thousand videos of sweeping your bald and an unattractive. I'm gonna have said. Oh, probably, you know
500 pounds as a joke
Well, I got like 900 panels out after my apples came out. I just
The people
On and made panels
And I put it and I said make this a geisha
And so it makes her look like
Ask her to marry you or alone obviously you're in love with the dumb
You don't shut up about every day, I always think that means you love her
When I wake up and I think of a girl all day and like, you know, that means you like her
Maybe now, but you definitely like
About one thing that is the real one that thing that is and I don't know is that ghost
The thing that is
And he became up last night I I talked more to Nick last night than I've ever talked to Nick in my life was a mute
Dude, I should
Have more for like six months and then one day he talked and he's like oh my god you talk
I was like I told you he talks dick I talked to Nick Johnson people
I was here to do the dolphin noise the dolphin noise. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I had the dolphin soundboard
Yeah, I was like looking for like a funny thing to play and then I said
Dolphin need her
Oh my god, oh my god
Can't look I can't look it's the most worst thing I ever saw in my life. Did we get bombed?
I thought it would be like a funny like sound like I like it like like flippery sound
I didn't know it's actually women having sex
Taking on a table, and there's a dolphin smiling on top of her, and I don't think it was yeah
It was a real
It was a real doll. Oh my god
That was shocking guys
Don't Google it. There was a guy in the 90s who jumped into a dolphin thing and he got arrested for fucking the dolphin
Dolphins supposedly are the smartest animals on the telepathic
Kind of looked like you site. He was
Yeah, you know what? Hey, but you know, it's funny. Is that how's market so where the dolphins like the Japanese?
Office of the smartest animals on earth
They were both
Another hippie who jumped in a fucking cage with an orca and
He jumped in a cage with a killer whale he tried to save it and it just ate him he tried to save it for more
Hey, so what are you doing? I mean the wife. We're going to Costco. We're gonna get some orange juice and shit
What are you doing today? I'm gonna jump in a cage with a killer whale
I would only go to my watch
Well, very different. That's a lot of sperm psyche. Don't get nasty
On it is like
More valuable in gold and it's pretty proud. It's called amber grease and it washes up if I came in your mouth
Would you swallow a thing of me to say? I spit it out into like a little like jar
Is that that is that a copy holding just for the cum?
Yeah, I knew it. I knew it. That's just the calm for the week, right? Or whatever
Horace you've had over you've been cheating on me by the way
No, you've been cheating on me a lot of with somebody
And I'm gonna just drink it one night. I'm moving the whole thing once it gets full
You've been filling on McDonald's couple of calm and now you're chugging chug a lugging
The problem is kind of dried out it kind of dries out and so it's like it takes a second forever
Very I've got buddies who eat like whales and seals
What are you gonna make it weird bro with the whale shit we're talking about come drinking here
Can I always make it weird?
We're talking about talking calm. Oh my god. Don't make it weird Canada where you will talk look up sex with dolphins
You have to do you have to look it up sometimes and you ever see that?
I just have to show you this picture. Oh my god of this woman. I can't believe it. Oh my god
Okay, I just have to show you this picture
Can you wait until I'm done taking a shit can I show you this video just wait oh
My god, kind of shit. You're shitting a Canadian shit. Hey, I'm taking a Canadian loggy
If I can drop in a log, that's I'm dropping a Canadian log a with maple syrup and everything
Did I just
Did I just eat peniche for a little baby, what am I watching?
You thought it would go bad, I didn't see it.
I'm sorry. I need to get this full screen guy. I mean, I can't get this bigger. I mean, this is this is great
That's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy, that's crazy
What the fuck?
You're paid, paid. That's the only little dolphin.
This is what taking a shallow page is like.
That's what you just witnessed, my man.
Holy fuck.
Man, isn't it fun?
Little Canadian dolphin, baby.
Is there one like no or that they can't even like type? I hope so. Is that dolphin look so happy though?
And there were a lot of laughing it wasn't like I mean that could have been a scary sight
He just said I hope no one's typing because they're dying laughing. That's funny. I hope that's why I mean I know that's why I'm not typing
Yeah, I see pages shaking your head like no no that wasn't good
That wasn't like but that woman had a good sense. You know, I think never wear like one of those
one of those um you know um cheetah print dresses in in the wild are you crazy that's the best
i think it's like i think it's some kind of signal to all the animals to have brother your cheetah
print oh g-string is what i live for bag give me psyche and his cheetah print puppies i need a
cheetah print okay somebody send me a cheetah print i'll wear it
Oh, we'll go have enough. I know he'll be on board. Okay. She don't print. She's
Somewhere in Papa New Guinea. There's a fucking cheetah dolphin running around
New Guinea what I think what else is that? That's like between Colombian and rulebook
That's where they fucking eat brain and then they decided that oh, we get crazy
Did you say the rain
Quack quack your quacker hit the link page hit the link to I need to hear that voice baby. Come on
You're burning joint where the fuck you all come up here with a little dolphin piano
Can I once I want a man to look at me someday like that dolphin look at that woman exactly?
But I know what you mean and it's down to that excited
Dolphin, but I know when I look at women that way that's all women want or whatever even men
I guess when they're gay, they just want someone to look at them like they mean everything on the planet to them
It's how you look at a person. I don't care and you just and you just mouth them in your hand like butter like oh
Like it's the way you look at someone. Yep. Easy. Go on. Easy. You're gonna you're gonna chip in for a
Speedo song and then I oh you're gonna make a magic mod by the way because a summer is magic mod and she'll kick him if he if he's here
Just to protect him. He's standard. Anyway, why not just make him
The what I'll always unhide him
All right. All right. All right. Cool. Just but be I will
Okay, it's I try I just try to like, um I know you keep the magic mask to minimum me and then say it basically
Maybe who a lecture where else you like one to I made like five people managing my remember
I'll be managing ma that day the next day like all of them had like left my show and by the way
There is um somebody um the Zara remember Zara that used to come on the show. Yes. That was a girl
Yeah, so I saw that she like someone came in recently like oh I'm dating Zara now and oh yeah she
she said she used to go and I saw that she was on so I went into her chat today and she was just
like walking around it was her and I said hey Zara it's been a while you know um but uh nice to
see you I hope you're well and then she didn't say anything and then I like left and I came back and
I'm blocked in her chat. I've never even been in. Wow. She has me blocked. I mean all the pre pre blocked
I mean that's that kind of was she bought the bullshit. She bought the bullshit
People going around talking shit about you. She might have caught a Wikipedia episode
like
it's insane, that's lander
like when people go around talking shit like that
she has what she wants now
she has like a bunch of simps
like it was basically like a bunch of guys
like just kissing her butt and stuff like that
which I mean I would have been friendly to her
in her chat, I mean I don't
I do like to like, you know, have fun in chats and stuff like that and I did see some people I know in the chat
But I couldn't talk in anyway, so I just left and Durban sold it, but it's like it's fine
It's like but I mean I've heard people just getting blocked from chats not even before they've never even been to the chat
I mean, how do they do that? I can't I don't know I can block people before they even
So I get big. Oh, it's because of the type in the comments
You can and before they come up on battle you could do that, you know, Zara was beautiful. She was she kind of looks like a like
I remember her I don't but I do like I remember I don't did she come up?
Yeah, she was like real pretty she was like
You know, I think she's Middle Eastern and she was like or Hispanic or something like that
And she was like real friendly and like I think she was like in the tarot to a little bit
And I got it
I don't know if she was like she had a deck or something
But then she was like kind of like on the fence is it evil or not?
And I think that she's gone in the I'm not part of her world
No, it's sad. Okay, so you don't need to be brought on don't
Whatever good riddance back then everything. I was her reason God puts people in your life and I'd like for a reason
She wasn't meant to be for a reason
Paragraph oh, yeah, there's a channel got I mean gossipers a better channel you can go say hi in her chat
I'm sure she's a pretty shit. Who else got to her by the way because they asked about me when I'm not here
And it's a little here. I don't know what a super is like. Okay. He here's I've gotten those being doxed and beat his chat and he
New like like nobody else even sweeties like oh, that's not doxing. I should know no my name or bailing anyway
So, um, but he but this person knew and he and then he got Christine's attention
Christine and I then that made up and so wow got gossipers is making things happen in this panel version, you know
Gossiper also
Is the gossiper?
Alex women it would
When is it for one minute? It's not for one minute. I don't know. There's somebody hide him already
And he's asking me to unhide him like I think that that's what I'm getting from that
I don't wait, but yeah, she won't she won't hide you. I'm you out for a few seconds. Well, she's cool though summer
She's here. No, I know she's not I don't think she right now, but she could be I mean it's like
I know she likes sometimes she's in the pack. I don't know why she blocked you. She never said anything about
Bad, but maybe but maybe I was wrong. Maybe it was like some kind of like like sometimes I've been blocked
You know what easy I can't do when I'm up here. Anyway, I got to be in the chat
But I got a drop off panel and like see if you got hit and then hit your name in and all that bullshit
It was kind of like I hadn't seen her like a year. So I was kind of excited. I was like, hey
I was like I thought I thought oh, she's gonna like get a real excited
Oh
Fucking Lisa Jordan is back
Yeah, at least it's been on now a few times. Um, I haven't been like I went to her show a few times and said hi and stuff like that
But I just haven't I haven't her shows like a
You know, she does it a lot less, and so it's like weird time she comes on, and then it's like, you know, we had the
She's still asking for it
Wait, now she's with us, there's this guy in her discord, and he's like, as I look at her discord, and there's this guy, and she's like, letting him take over the discord, and he's like real weird
I think he has like guns and stuff like that, and he's always like posting like just a weird, like
That doesn't make sense, she's such a sweet little
Yeah, I don't want to be around his guns. Yeah, maybe one of her mom
But shorty, I don't think I've ever been to her channel though
I got that's weird because it's like because really he's looking for a good co-host man to make a shit pop
Like yeah, and there's a lot of people
It's like I want to go down there. You know we would like I would like in the fight with there
Just for content or something for so she would have like fun content and stuff
You know, I saw a lot of the other day my friend
many Manson oh yeah and I was rolling my pants man die motherfucker you know
funny shit he was just you know I was dying I was hysterical died it was like
300 people watching and he was like fuck you all fuck you
I was gonna type in the chat and actually send a super chat like maybe remember me from psyches, but
Control
Yeah, I don't give a fuck what many is man. That she he is hilarious
Yeah, he's out of control
Now that is content. Jesus fucking Christ. Yeah
That's actually a good song. Yeah, like remember when he was on my show and he did like an eye in this. Yeah
Rainbow connection. He sent you stickers. He performed. He's still doing it
But he's charging five hours or so long and no one sends money, right? And he gets pissed. He's like fuck you
I'm going to come in and shut the shit down if I don't get five hours
I ain't no appear for fucking now sing from and then people start singing or sending money
And he's like personal Jesus. Fuck you. I hate my neighbor downstairs. Fuck all of you
It's the funny shit I've ever seen. Yeah, you take out mini mansons
Shout out to many
Mini Manson one of my first guests and I mean I had like an exciting like first six months when I had like
I had I had from the Howard Stern show
I had shooley come in and bomb my show with like in a wig more than a blonde
He's wearing a blonde wig like I later and he and be sort of fighting with them and stuff
I'm like, yeah, this is a celebrity kind of it's like kind of like a those people are not celebrities
Well, I watch Howard Stern's a celebrity. Yeah, but then I don't want to say it's a celebrity
Well, I think in the 2000s and 2010
very Jewish producer named Shuley who now has a show and everything but yeah so but he's he was one of his producers and like a big part of the show and
I miss in the morning he would give him competition remember I miss in the morning
Howard there was either Howard Stern or I miss
yeah and Don I miss it's such a like a
curmudgeon and so so unhappy
Oh, no, they still sit there shit every day because my boss would pick me up and all the way to the city because they love that shit
Hated that shit listen to that dick. He was like so he was like wearing this cowboy out almost like the cowboy hat
And just he was like the whitest. I don't know
And then how it's done comes on and it's like a breath of pressure like our
Yeah
I mean, but if you think about it, like, oh my gosh, how like, you know how much like Howard made and how much Robin made compared to like Howard, but she still made a good money, like, like, you know, but he made Oprah money and she was making Steadman money, you know, so I was still kind of bad pretty cheap with his.
He always let you know like the company be part of the negotiation, but then he'd always get dragged into these negotiations and stuff
He lost Jackie that he was big time and she was with some little black lady
He's caused in a booth like then I'm gonna give her a million
And I said I said I had said I wanted alexandra to be my like my the Robin
We're quivers to my Howard and she got so yeah
I mean, oh yeah, oh my god, that would definitely insult her come on
I mean, I was like just ridiculous, but yeah, I mean it's like and then she said it also because but then when I was friends with her
She said I she said she liked what I did for black people because I made I made her look so great in her video
And she said she said oh because my family used to like me the first black doll and stuff like that like like you know
And so that's what she said. So I mean, I don't I don't know you had an easier time letting go of Alexandra than a beta
Obviously because
Alexandra I still have hope with Alexander. I don't have any hope. I mean hope the bitch hate you. What do you say?
This is why you're crazy. Why do you have hope?
She'll like me. Oh god. No, no, it's different like me and summer have hope
Easy and summer have hope you and I Xanjia don't have hope. This is like real evil hatred shit
She does not think you know, we don't talk that way about each other as much as
I've never said anything is bad about about um about her then you said about summer and christian and stuff like that
But they still like you
I mean, it's like, and she's no, no, no, no, but it's definitely the way they talk about youth.
Just like, I like how I hate him.
Leave me alone.
He's I'm not I'm almost out of my straight, you know, straight, straight criminal.
It's more interesting than just like some gay loser and the lies, the lies, the slander, the lies.
I mean, did she strike my channel?
No, Bita struck my channel.
So she did.
Strike strike. It said you got a strike from this person on YouTube. You got the email everything astray. Yeah, what?
For what for because I because I'm tripp cake
I play the tripp cake video that had like a second where you put at the end of her and her boy her boyfriend that thumbnail
That I did that I took down for but then she didn't like say oh
Can you take you put a thumbnail up and she struck you? Yeah
And I she's never struck anyone before so I guess I must have been this the worst person
I've been saying out of all the people that don't shit to a palm bomb there and she strikes you but sometimes don't know
Well that shows you something. Oh my god. I was like, hey, I'm gonna strike you sweet pee if you don't take down my strike
and then she went totally on the defense for sweepy like totally
So you have one strike against you at the moment if you get another one like the batless
Yeah
Yeah, it's like real like it's real looking real bad. You know, it's this one. Don't do it. Yeah
so I don't know like I did and she could take it back right supposedly they have an option
She could take it down. No way
RG took his dad and like or the person to get down in like three ten seconds after people snub before they can do
Yeah, also balls. Also. She could have said oh take it down right away
And like or you'll get a strike and so no she went for right give the strike right away. Oh, it's getting worn you
straight nope
No, mm-hmm, but I miss you the bitch is gone. She's like a white scorn, bro. Stop talking about her
I'm telling just
People and talking about me and then it's like I have
No, tell me why do you love us so much?
I just trauma bonded and
Okay, there you go. So that that's a story. That's what I'm saying. Why you're trauma bonded with her, okay?
It's like a carrot. It's like a you have a you know a mule, right? Oh, okay. Walks you put a carrot on a stick in front of it
And it's right here. It's like right dangling in his face. It's so close. It's like it'll be so good
But then it's like one step the care that you in your mind that bitch was holding a carrot in front of your head the whole time
Yes, Alex and then pull that out. It's a great. Yeah, the person won't she's like a person bugs bunny
who are we? Yeah, Persian Bugs Bunny. Oh, my God. That's
the funny. He should have a dick. Oh, I'm sorry to laugh while
we're getting to the bottom of things, but you gotta keep
the sense of humor. That's fucking funny. So the Persian
Bugs Bunny bitch held the stupid carrot in front of your
head. And your poor Roni's like, Oh, I love you. The carrot
give me the carrot. And she was like, haha, no carrot for you
loser. And I'm going to strike you. Yeah. Yeah. That's
And it's my fault because I'm bad because oh my god. I doxxed her boy
Let me know her boyfriend's name. It's it's apparently Mohammed and stuff
Laughing about it, so they didn't care she doesn't care. She just hates me. That's a thing
She was laughing when RG said his name and or if people were saying his name in the check
She's laughing about sorry. I said the n word about him the other day supposedly
Played it. Oh, that was the hard. Oh, it's okay. Yeah, it was because you know black RG. I don't is he blank?
It's that's why it's called black RG, right?
He's a black voice. All right, so I got pissed. I don't know. It's just like black RG. You mean the black
Minute
That's exactly he sounds like
No black RG has the funniest lap
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Oh, here we go. Canada Ghost is in the studio. I don't know if I should list this for, oh, they left, okay.
Is that Canada Ghost?
So, when even Canada Ghost came up and then they disappeared.
Yo, Canada and me have been all alone, by the way, on Canada's panel that you just saw.
Nobody even noticed that Alexander McQueen is Alexander McQueen, our CMP.
What if Alexander is?
What if you're Alexander McQueen?
Yeah, even the Terry Police. Nobody notices anything up here, Canada.
But me and Canada have been all alone you guys didn't come up to say hello you left us all alone
Me in Canada all alone see for two nights. Just hanging out
You know
Again and you guys don't come up to say hello
That's crazy. I'm gonna be pissed. I'm gonna be pissed
Play girl. See that's me. You're not to me. Stop doxing me dick. That's exactly what I look like
Literally expect me what I look like. Nobody's diaphragm is that wide that was crazy
Let's go airborne of mine is I live in the dog. Go back. That was so I'm telling you that's exactly me
Guy your back is not behind your arms. It's just
Hey, it's a David Hasselhoff anything's possible. You know
Exactly
He's I mean he's a star that goes goes. What the fuck is oh, we got it. We'll put the barrel
It could be a couple dum-dums up here. I want to talk to you. So
You get too happy you gotta put the wall up make sure it's gold
Yeah, I was making fun of Canada fucking thing. That isn't oh my god. I like think that could be
How was you and how was your analysis panel going?
It's good man
Yeah, but you haven't
Another person's panel posted his link into somebody else's panel. I was like if you're that desperate
I might as well fucking see what's going on and it was you that's for what that's
Bye what that's been losing
But I did I did show up
What were you wearing?
Psycho finish all like he didn't
I have my own hey fuckers. Hey fuckers. He's like in the script. No, my favorite is hey fucker
Carla, yeah
Yeah, you guys can write the book
you're fine. I would sneak into ghost house and fuck his mom without him knowing hey ghost did
you see that you know my mom died literally like six months ago so that was very yeah she died after
I fucked her really good. Wait where'd she bury because I'm gonna I'm gonna fucking take her up and
piss on her face.
So this is awesome it all coincides
What cemetery bro, just give me the alley. I'm a pull-up son. I'll pull up
Do you guys remember that Seinfeld episode where George is at the office and he makes the joke?
He's like, I fucked your wife. Ah, and and he's oh, we got poem bomb. We got poem bomb to psyche poem bomb himself